Why we stopped
using WordPress
Ashley Christian  ·  Groundbreaker Marketing
we used to use
WordPress
which was sort of
the industry
standard for
marketing
agencies
Probably most of
you have a
WordPress
website
but because of
the day and age
of AI
we now build them
on Astro which is
a static website
and we build it
with Claude Code
if those words
mean nothing to
you that's
totally fine it's
just a modern way
of building a
website and it's
not hard to do
honestly I don't
want to make it
sound like it's
the hardest thing
in the world it's
actually much
harder to build a
WordPress website
than it is to
build an AI
driven website
What's hard is to
build a website
the right way
that has the
right
information
That's going to
be the right
trust signals to
Google so that
you're showing up
first
And also that
when someone does
land on your
site
they're
converting to a
customer